http://www.timesnews.net/site/privacy.html

E-Paper
At Kingsport Times News, we are committed to giving you quality service. As part of that commitment, we gather information about customers, users of our website, www.timesnews.net (the “Site”), social media sites, and other services, as well as visitors so we can better serve you. Kingsport Times News recognizes that the privacy and security of personal information is important to you. Because it is also important to us, we have implemented this Privacy Policy to tell you (1) what information we collect; (2) how we use that information; (3) with whom we may share it; (4) the choices you can make about how we collect, use, and share your information; and (5) how you can access our information about you.Your use of our Site is acceptance and agreement to the practices that are described in this Privacy Policy, which is incorporated as part of the Terms of Use governing this website.1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT1.1 Information You ProvideKingsport Times News collects information in different ways when you interact with us, including when you:Make purchases from us;Create an account on our website;Visit our social media sitesSend us communications through email; andRequest to receive newsletters, notifications, or other communications from us.Information you submit may include your name, email address, address, username and password, payment information, and information about your person. Entering one of our contests or sweepstakes, submitting an employment application, or using one of our community functions may involve our collection of further information from you.1.2 Automatically Collected InformationWe obtain and retain certain information automatically when you interact with our Site, emails, and online advertising. We use this information to enhance our services, create a more personalized experience, evaluate the operation and use of our Site, and to support our marketing campaigns. When you access and interact with the Site, we may collect certain information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the Site, our servers receive and record information about your computer, device, and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the Site from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device, geolocation data, or other transactional information for that device. We may collect this information using “cookies” and other website technologies (i.e., browser pixels, beacons, and Adobe flash technology).“Cookies” and other website technologies are comprised of small bits of data that often include a de-identified or anonymous unique identifier. Websites, apps, and other services send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that service. These technologies may also be used to collect and store information about your usage of the Site, such as pages you have visited, content you have viewed, search queries you have run and advertisements you have seen.Most browsers offer instructions on how to manage, control, and delete cookies in the Help section of the toolbar. You can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. You can also manually delete cookies from your computers. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features, content, or personalization available through the Site.Third parties that support the Site by providing services, such as tracking aggregate Site usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information. Kingsport Times News does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies.1.3 Information from other SourcesWe may supplement the information we collect with information from other sources, such as publicly available information from social media services, commercially available sources and information from our business partners.2. USE AND DISCLOSURE2.1 Business Use and DisclosureWe use your information to offer and provide our products and services and to perform our business operations, including order or service fulfillment, internal business processes, marketing, authentication, loss and fraud prevention, public safety and legal functions. Examples of these functions include:To provide the services you request;To measure and improve the Site and other features.To improve your experience with the Site by providing content you may find relevant and interesting.To provide you with support and to respond to inquiries.To allow third-party service providers – such as contractors, agents, or sponsors – to assist us in providing and managing the Site and performing the services you request from us.To contact you and send materials and notifications related to the Site and Kingsport Times News.Sandusky Newspapers, Inc. ("SNI") is the parent company of Kingsport Times News. Accordingly, if you provide information to any of the businesses or websites owned or operated by SNI, we may merge and share that information with other current or future SNI entities, including affiliates and subsidiaries. We may also share personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or similar event. When the information collected from or about you does not identify you as a specific person, we may use that information for any purpose or share it with third parties.2.2 Other Use and DisclosureThere may be instances when Kingsport Times News may disclose your information where Kingsport Times News has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to:Protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of Kingsport Times News, our employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements and our terms of use);Protect the safety, privacy, and security of users of the Site or members of the public;Protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; andComply with the law or legal process.3. USER ACCESS AND CONTROLIf you would like to access, review, correct, update, or otherwise request that we modify use of your personal information you have previously provided directly to us, you may contact using the information below. In your request, please include your email address, name, address, and telephone number and specify clearly what information you would like to access, change, update, or suppress. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. For California residents, you may request that we not share your personal information on a going forward basis with unaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes by emailing the contact provided above. We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable.If you want to stop receiving materials and notification, you can contact us at the information below or by following the unsubscribe instruction that may appear in such communications. There are certain service notification communications that you may not opt-out of, such as notifications of changes to the Site or policies.By postal mail: 65 N. Main, Chagrin Falls OH 44922By email: legal@sanduskynewspapers.com4. CHILDRENThe Site is for a general audience and is not intended for use by children under 13 years of age without permission from their parent or legal guardian. Kingsport Times News does not knowingly collect information from children under 13 years of age. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and believe your child has disclosed personally identifiable information please contact us and we will work to delete that information.5. STEPS WE TAKE TO PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATIONKingsport Times News works to use reasonable security measures to protect the confidentiality and integrity of personal information. For example, personal information maintained in hard copy records may be kept in locked locations or cabinets. We restrict the number of employees who have access to certain personal information. Employees who violate our privacy and security policies are subject to disciplinary action up to and including termination. We require the service providers who have access to your information to maintain the security of your information. We also mandate that our service providers only use the information solely for providing the services we request. We also work to use reasonable safeguards to protect your information in electronic format. However, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of your information, so any information you provide to us is done so at your own risk.6. OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION6.1 Location of DataThe Site is hosted in and managed from the United States. If you are a user located outside the United States, you understand and consent to having any personal information processed in the United States. United States data protection and other relevant laws may not be the same as those in your jurisdiction. This includes the use of cookies and other tracking technologies as described above. As a result, please read this Privacy Policy with care.6.2 Linked ServicesThe Site may also be linked to sites operated by unaffiliated companies, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, newsletters, or applications developed and maintained by unaffiliated companies. Kingsport Times News is not responsible for the privacy practices of unaffiliated companies, and once you leave the Site or click an advertisement you should check the applicable privacy policy of the other service.6.3 Comment PolicyUnder the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, comments are the sole responsibility of the individual commenters. Kingsport Times News reserves the right to delete any comments that include hate speech, libel, plagiarism, threats, personal attacks or off-topic assertions, and inappropriate language in order to protect the integrity of the site and its users. We do not edit comments for content.7. UPDATES TO PRIVACY POLICYThis Privacy Policy was posted and is effective as of 2008. It was last updated on December 27, 2017. Kingsport Times News may modify this Privacy Policy over time, so please check the effective date to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Site.This Privacy Policy was last updated December 27, 2017.
Times News ePaper
To view our latest e-Edition click the image on the left.
© Copyright 2020 Kingsport Times News, 701 Lynn Garden Kingsport, TN | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
